- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
all: SpongeBob SquarePants!
- Ready?
所有：海绵宝宝！
- 准备好？
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
[laughing]
[笑]
♪ ♪
[waves crashing]
[海浪拍打]
[upbeat ukulele music]
[欢快的尤克里里音乐]
♪ ♪
[andante rock music]
[行板摇滚乐]
both: Dribble, dribble,
dribble, dribble,
两者：运球，运球，
运球，运球，
dribble--
- Hm?
运球——
- 嗯？
both: Dribble, dribble,
dribble, dribble,
两者：运球，运球，
运球，运球，
dribble, dribble,
- Agh!
both: Dribble, dribble,
- 啊啊！
两者：运球，运球，
dribble, dribble.
运球，运球。
Dribble, dribble,
dribble, dribble.
运球，运球，
运球，运球。
Dribble, dribble,
dribble, dribble.
运球，运球，
运球，运球。
- Agh!
- 啊啊！
both: Dribble, dribble,
dribble, dribble,
两者：运球，运球，
运球，运球，
- It's been ten minutes!
- 已经十分钟了！
Ain't you gonna shoot?
你不打算开枪吗？
both: Dribble, dribble,
dribble, dribble,
两者：运球，运球，
运球，运球，
dribble, dribble,
dribble, dribble--
运球，运球——
♪ ♪
- Sorry, but you boys
were slower
- 抱歉，你们这些孩子
速度较慢
than a Sunday afternoon.
比周日下午。
♪ ♪
On your mark,
get set, eat!
在你的标记上，
摆好姿势，吃饭！
[anticipatory vocalizations]
[预期发声]
[elegant pizzicato music]
[优雅的拨奏音乐]
- Wow, you two are off
like a herd of turtles.
- 哇，你们两个走了
就像一群乌龟。
Watch this!
注意这个！
[frantic ukulele music]
[疯狂的尤克里里音乐]
♪ ♪
I win.
我赢了。
[dejected music]
[沮丧的音乐]
♪ ♪
Hot dang!
热当当！
I'm faster than green grass
through a goose!
我比绿草还快
通过一只鹅！
Hm, these jumbo dogs
are much too big
嗯，这些巨型狗
太大了
for your baby heads.
为了你的宝宝头。
[frantic music]
[疯狂的音乐]
These dinky dogs
should do ya.
这些小狗狗
应该做你。
♪ ♪
both: [muffled] Thank you.
两人：[低声]谢谢。
- You're welcome!
- 不客气！
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚乐]
♪ ♪
I win again!
我又赢了！
That's right!
这是正确的！
[all yelling, groaning]
[所有人大喊大叫，呻吟]
I own all of y'all!
我拥有你们所有人！
Yeehaw!
耶哈！
- Sandy, don't you think
you're playing
- 桑迪，你不觉得吗
你正在玩
a teensy-weensy bit rough?
有点粗糙？
Just a smidge?
Hm?
只是一点点？
嗯？
- Aww, I'm actually going
a little easy on you guys,
- 哇哦，我真的要去
对你们稍微宽松一点
seein' as how
you're all so delicate.
看看如何
你们都是那么的脆弱。
[all yell]
[全都喊]
Hey, who wants to play
"dodge the chum"?
嘿嘿，谁想玩啊
“躲开密友”？
- No, I don't think I'm--
[gibbers]
- 不，我不认为我是--
[胡言乱语]
Sandy is really
stressing me out today.
桑迪确实是
今天让我压力很大。
You want to go jellyfishing?
你想去捉水母吗？
- No, I'd rather
go jellyfishing.
- 不，我宁愿
去钓水母。
- You sure you don't wanna go
jellyfishing?
- 你确定你不想去
捕水母？
- I said no.
- 我说不。
I wanna go jellyfishing.
我想去钓水母。
- Okay, we'll do
what you want.
- 好的，我们会做的
你想要什么。
[both giggling]
[两人都咯咯笑]
- The name is Sandy Cheeks,
- 我的名字是桑迪·奇克斯，
and I can lick any critter
on any beach!
我可以舔任何小动物
在任何海滩上！
[carefree orchestral music]
[悠闲的管弦乐]
[both laughing]
[两人都笑了]
♪ ♪
- Now this is fun!
- 现在这很有趣！
- [mock RP accent] Yes, quite
the civilized sport, eh, what?
- [模拟 RP 口音] 是的，相当
文明体育，呃，什么？
- [laughs]
- [笑]
[mock RP accent] I say,
[模拟 RP 口音]我说，
No more rough-horsing.
[laughs]
别再胡闹了。
[笑]
- [Southern accent] And no more
you-know-who
- [南方口音] 没有了
神秘人
killing the casual vibe.
破坏了休闲的氛围。
[both yell]
- Hey, guys!
[两人大喊]
- 嘿，伙计们！
[both gibber]
[两人都胡言乱语]
- Mind if I join you?
- 介意我加入吗？
both: [weakly] Not at all.
两人：[弱弱地]一点也不。
- Great!
I can't wait to kick
- 伟大的！
我已经等不及要踢了
some jelly booty!
一些果冻战利品！
- Uh, the thing is, Sandy,
in jellyfishing,
- 呃，问题是，桑迪，
在捕捉水母的过程中，
we don't play to kick booty.
我们玩游戏不是为了赚钱。
We actually catch and release
the little sea angels.
我们实际上捕获并释放
小海天使们。
- Well, that sounds
about as exciting
- 嗯，听起来
大约同样令人兴奋
as tap water soup.
作为自来水汤。
Oh, well.
Your game, your rules.
那好吧。
你的游戏，你的规则。
[both grunt]
[两人咕哝]
[jellyfish buzzing]
[水母嗡嗡声]
[sprightly orchestral music]
【轻快的管弦乐】
- [laughs]
- [笑]
He's in mine now!
他现在在我的里面了！
- [laughs]
Now he's in mine!
- [笑]
现在他在我的里面了！
♪ ♪
- [laughs]
- [笑]
[jellyfish buzzing]
[水母嗡嗡声]
♪ ♪
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- [flatly] Whoopee.
[growls]
- [平淡]哎呀。
[咆哮]
[yells]
Whoo-hoo!
[喊叫]
呼呼！
You're gonna look good
mounted on my wall!
你会看起来不错
安装在我的墙上！
- Uh-uh.
Catch and release, Sandy.
- 呃呃。
抓住然后释放，桑迪。
- Hm.
- 嗯。
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- Well, this is lamer
than a paper sandwich.
- 嗯，这是拉默
比纸三明治。
Hey!
Ooh!
嘿！
哦！
This one's fat as a tick!
这个胖得像蜱虫一样！
Ha, ha!
Got you!
哈，哈！
明白了！
- Huh.
The jelly-thingies
- 嗯。
果冻状的东西
were here a minute ago.
一分钟前还在这里。
- It isn't like them
to be so... coy.
- 这不像他们
如此……腼腆。
- [laughs]
[shudders]
- [笑]
[颤抖]
[laughs] I guess they must've--
[shudders]
[笑]我想他们一定是——
[颤抖]
Gotten sick of the boring game!
厌倦了无聊的游戏！
[shudders]
[颤抖]
Hm?
Mm!
嗯？
毫米！
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
Get in here,
you slimy varmint!
进入这里，
你这个粘糊糊的害虫！
Hm?
- SpongeBob, look!
嗯？
- 海绵宝宝，看！
How's it going, little guy?
怎么样，小家伙？
- [growls]
- [咆哮]
So that's how you wanna
play it.
所以这就是你想要的
玩它。
[dark music]
[黑暗音乐]
[sprightly orchestral music]
【轻快的管弦乐】
Hi-ya!
嗨呀！
I'm catching and releasing--
我抓住并释放——
releasing them
from their freedom!
释放他们
脱离他们的自由！
♪ ♪
- Hey, widdle jewwy bewwy.
- 嘿，犹太犹太人。
Would you mind?
你会介意的？
- [grunts]
Mine!
- [咕哝]
我的！
[laughs]
[笑]
- What?
Ugh.
- 什么？
啊。
- Yeah!
- 是的！
[chuckles]
Easier than slipping
[笑声]
比滑倒还容易
down a mudslide!
滑下泥石流！
[jellyfish buzz]
Okay, okay.
[水母嗡嗡声]
好吧，好吧。
I know.
Catch and release.
我知道。
抓住并释放。
[energetic music]
[充满活力的音乐]
Isn't there anything more
to this game?
难道还有什么吗
到这个游戏？
- What more can anyone want?
- 任何人还想要什么？
- Yeah, it's perfect!
- 是的，太完美了！
- I have an idea how we can...
- 我有一个想法，我们怎样才能...
kick things up a notch!
让事情更上一层楼！
- Hey, Sandy,
I really don't think
- 嘿，桑迪，
我真的不认为
we need to kick anything up
any notches.
我们需要把一切都搞起来
任何凹口。
- Ha!
Frankenstein Fish Food!
- 哈！
弗兰肯斯坦鱼食！
Ooh, this should be fun!
哦，这应该很有趣！
[chuckles]
[笑声]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
♪ ♪
[jellyfish start]
[水母开始]
♪ ♪
Ha, ha!
That's what I'm talking about!
哈，哈！
这就是我要说的！
They're no longer jellyfish.
它们不再是水母了。
Now they're jelly-buzz saws!
现在它们是果冻锯！
♪ ♪
- [yells]
- [大喊]
- Ah!
Oh.
- 啊！
哦。
Hey!
嘿！
You're supposed to fly
into there!
你应该飞翔
到那里去！
♪ ♪
Hm?
嗯？
[grunting, straining]
[咕哝，用力]
♪ ♪
[screaming]
[尖叫]
♪ ♪
I'm a walking glow stick!
我是行走的荧光棒！
[screams]
[尖叫声]
- Whoa, Nelly, little jelly!
- 哇，耐莉，小果冻！
[yelling, gibbering]
[大喊大叫，胡言乱语]
Ow.
噢。
Such a soothing pastime.
这是一种令人舒缓的消遣。
[rousing orchestral music]
[振奋人心的管弦乐]
- [yelling]
- [大喊]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
♪ ♪
- Thank you, super Sandy!
- 谢谢你，超级桑迪！
- Welcome to
the jellyfish rodeo!
- 欢迎来到
水母竞技！
♪ ♪
Aha!
啊哈！
Gotcha, varmint!
明白了，害虫！
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
- [yells]
- [大喊]
- Hey, that is not
how we do it.
- 嘿，那不是
我们如何做。
[gibbering]
[胡言乱语]
Carry on.
继续。
- Hands off that jellyfish,
SpongeBob!
- 放开那只水母
海绵宝宝！
He's mine!
他是我的！
Oh, you are so mine!
哦，你真是我的人！
- No...
Problem.
- 没问题。
Oy.
哎哟。
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
♪ ♪
- You're out!
- 你出去了！
Hit the showers!
去淋浴吧！
Hm?
嗯？
Time for spring cleaning!
春季大扫除的时间到了！
[frantic music]
[疯狂的音乐]
♪ ♪
Into the dustbin
of history!
进垃圾箱
历史！
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
Heh.
呵呵。
[ululates]
[哀嚎]
♪ ♪
[both yell]
[两人大喊]
♪ ♪
- Ha!
Hoo-ah!
- 哈！
呼啊！
♪ ♪
Hyah!
哈！
♪ ♪
Whammer, bammer,
in the slammer!
猛击，猛击，
在猛烈撞击中！
Whoo-hoo!
呼呼！
I'm the queen
of Jellyfish Fields!
我是女王
水母田！
How does that feel, losers?
失败者们，感觉如何？
- [hoarsely] I don't like it.
- [沙哑]我不喜欢它。
[quiet ukulele music]
[安静的尤克里里音乐]
- I can't see or hear you,
- 我看不到或听不到你
for my face
has been cauterized.
为了我的脸
已被烧灼。
- Ah, you guys are just
out of shape.
- 啊，你们只是
变形了。
Come on,
best two out of three.
来吧，
三分之二最好。
- [wheezes]
- [喘息声]
- [strains]
- [菌株]
But you've got
all the jellyfish.
但你有
所有的水母。
- And there's no more field.
- 没有更多的领域了。
- [gasps]
Oh?
- [喘气]
哦？
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
[laughs]
Did I do that?
[笑]
我这样做了吗？
- [whines]
Yes.
- [哀嚎]
是的。
- You did this, too.
- 你也这么做了。
- I guess I can be
overly competitive at times.
- 我想我可以
有时竞争过度。
- Gee, you think?
- 哎呀，你觉得呢？
Ow!
噢！
Gah!
嘎！
- You guys'll be all right
- 你们会没事的
if you just walk it off.
如果你只是走开它。
[dejected ukulele music]
[沮丧的尤克里里音乐]
♪ ♪
- Don't forget
to release 'em.
- 别忘了
释放他们。
♪ ♪
- Oh? Hm?
[gasps]
- 哦？嗯？
[喘气]
Yeah!
That problem is solved.
是的！
这个问题就解决了。
Now to my other problem.
现在我的另一个问题。
♪ ♪
Ah, I've got
some deep-dish thinking to do
啊，我有
一些深层次的思考要做
about my aggressive ways.
关于我的攻击性方式。
♪ ♪
[jellyfish buzzing]
[水母嗡嗡声]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
[tranquil music]
[安静的音乐]
Om.
唵。
♪ ♪
[gong crashes]
Om.
[锣声响起]
唵。
♪ ♪
Om.
唵。
Turns out, I'm the best
at relaxing, too.
事实证明我是最棒的
在放松时也是如此。
- Om.
- 唵。
[both screaming]
[两人尖叫]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
- Oh, Sandy, help!
- It's horrible!
- 哦，桑迪，救命！
- 太可怕了！
[both gibbering]
[两人都胡言乱语]
[buzzing]
[嗡嗡声]
♪ ♪
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
- Oh, Sandy, help!
It's--
- 哦，桑迪，救命！
它是 -
[screams]
Oh.
[尖叫声]
哦。
[tranquil music]
[安静的音乐]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
- [roars]
- [咆哮]
- Ah, brother SpongeBob.
- 啊，海绵宝宝兄弟。
Brother Patrick.
帕特里克兄弟。
I bow to your good natures.
我向你的善良本性致敬。
What can I do for you?
我能为你做什么？
- You can clobber that
giant jellyfish monster thing!
- 你可以破坏它
巨型水母怪物！
- Yeah, smash it up good!
=> - 是的，粉碎它好！
- Oh, I couldn't do that.
- 哦，我做不到。
I'm non-violent now.
我现在是非暴力的。
I wouldn't hurt a fly-fish.
我不会伤害飞鱼。
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
[screaming]
[尖叫]
♪ ♪
- [roars]
- [咆哮]
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
[roars]
[怒吼]
- How about
some soothing music, jellyfish?
- 怎么样
一些舒缓的音乐，水母？
[tranquil music]
[安静的音乐]
♪ ♪
A soothing sitar
always brings me peace.
舒缓的西塔琴
总是给我带来平静。
♪ ♪
- Mm.
- 毫米。
♪ ♪
- Oh!
- 哦！
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
[rock music]
[摇滚乐]
- Whoa!
Ow!
- 哇！
噢！
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
- Oh...
- 哦...
The gongs!
They always calm me down.
锣！
他们总是让我平静下来。
[jellyfish roars]
[水母咆哮]
Ah!
啊!
[all yelling]
[大家大喊]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
[gongs crash]
[锣声响起]
Om.
唵。
all: Om.
众：唵。
- [roars]
- [咆哮]
all: Om.
众：唵。
- [roars]
- [咆哮]
- [growls]
Okay, that does it.
- [咆哮]
好的，这样就可以了。
I was a pacifist, but now
I'm gonna pass my fist
我曾经是一个和平主义者，但现在
我要递出我的拳头
through your face!
通过你的脸！
Mm.
毫米。
As destroyer and transformer,
作为毁灭者和变形者，
I transform to destroy you.
我变身就是为了毁灭你。
- [growls]
- [咆哮]
- Put up your dukes
and fight me like a squirrel!
- 摆出你的公爵
像松鼠一样与我战斗！
[combative music]
[战斗音乐]
[both yelling]
[两人大喊]
[yelling, grunting]
[大喊大叫，咕哝]
♪ ♪
Hiya!
Oh!
嗨！
哦！
[moans]
Whoa!
[呻吟声]
哇！
- Sandy, catch!
- 桑迪，接住！
♪ ♪
- The universe gave us
a terrible weapon
- 宇宙给了我们
可怕的武器
made up of the darkest
dark matter
由最黑暗的组成
暗物质
just for this occasion.
就为了这个场合。
Ever played "dodge the chum"?
玩过“躲避密友”吗？
♪ ♪
- Mm?
- 毫米？
[roars]
[怒吼]
- Hey, get your slimy mitts
off my pals!
- 嘿，拿起你的粘糊糊的手套
离开我的朋友们！
Hiya!
Ya!
嗨！
呀！
♪ ♪
Whoa!
哇！
[growls]
Hiya!
[咆哮]
嗨！
♪ ♪
Nothing.
That's it!
没有什么。
就是这样！
[yells]
[喊叫]
- [chuckles]
- [轻笑]
Hm?
[yells]
嗯？
[喊叫]
- Pretty.
- Oh...
- 漂亮的。
- 哦...
[tranquil music]
[安静的音乐]
♪ ♪
[both giggling]
[两人都咯咯笑]
- Hm?
Oh.
- 嗯？
哦。
- Mm.
- 毫米。
- Who are my good
little jellies?
- 谁是我的好人
小果冻？
You are.
你是。
- Here you go.
Buy yourself something nice.
- 干得好。
给自己买点好东西吧
- [obliging buzz]
- [嗡嗡声]
- [giggles]
- [咯咯笑]
- Well, let's get
these little jellies
- 好吧，让我们开始吧
这些小果冻
back to their home.
回到他们的家。
[upbeat ukulele music]
[欢快的尤克里里音乐]
[laughs]
They really are sweet.
[笑]
他们真的很甜蜜。
[shudders]
[growls]
[颤抖]
[咆哮]
I'm gonna destroy you!
我要毁了你！
[growls]
[咆哮]
- That's our Sandy.
- 那是我们的桑迪。
- Yeah.
Hm?
- 是的。
嗯？
Which one's Sandy?
哪个是桑迪？
[laughs]
[笑]
♪ ♪
- [scatting]
- [分散]
♪ ♪
Catch.
抓住。
Oh, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot.
哦，热，热，热，热，热。
♪ ♪
Ah!
Yow!
啊!
哟！
Oh, oh!
Hot, hot, hot!
哦，哦！
热，热，热！
Hot mustard!
热芥末！
Oh! Oh! Whoa!
哦！哦！哇！
- You mind?
Can't you see
- 你介意吗？
你看不到吗
I'm trying to read here?
我想在这里读书？
- Oh.
Oh.
- 哦。
哦。
[intriguing music]
[有趣的音乐]
- Hm?
[growls]
- 嗯？
[咆哮]
- [scatting]
- [分散]
♪ ♪
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
- You have a loose thread.
- 你的线头松动了。
- Hm?
So?
- 嗯？
所以？
- I want to pull it.
- 我想拉它。
- Hm.
If I let you pull it,
- 嗯。
如果我让你拉它
will you please let me read
my book in peace?
请让我读一下好吗
我的书平安吗？
- Mm-hm.
- 嗯嗯。
- Fine.
Get it over with.
- 美好的。
快点结束吧。
- [giggles]
- [咯咯笑]
[excited gibbering]
[兴奋的胡言乱语]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- [growls]
- [咆哮]
[cash register dings]
[收银机叮叮声]
- Hm?
Ooh.
- 嗯？
哦。
- Ah!
- 啊！
[whines]
[哀鸣]
♪ ♪
- [excited gibbering]
- [兴奋的胡言乱语]
- [startled gasp]
- [惊呼]
Nobody look down!
没有人往下看！
- My leg of my pants!
- 我的裤腿！
- Hm.
- 嗯。
Seat yourself, sir.
坐下吧，先生。
I'll be with you
in a minute.
我会和你在一起
一分钟后。
[romantic orchestral music]
【浪漫的管弦乐】
- Me most valuable possession,
- 我最宝贵的财产，
except, of course,
当然，除了
for you, my love.
为了你，我的爱人。
Ah.
啊。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
[confused grunt]
[困惑的咕噜声]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
Me appreciation
is depreciating!
我欣赏
正在贬值！
Ah!
No!
啊!
不！
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no!
不，不，不，不，
不，不，不！
One dollar?
一美元？
[cries]
[哭声]
- I demand a refund!
- 我要求退款！
- Uh, what's the problem
here, sir?
- 呃，有什么问题吗
在这里，先生？
- There is a hair
in my soup,
- 有一根头发
在我的汤里，
and I demand a refund!
我要求退款！
- Eh...
Ooh.
- 呃...
哦。
Uh, well, that's not just
any hair, sir.
呃，好吧，这不仅仅是
任何头发，先生。
It's from the elusive
Peruvian jelly-lope,
它来自难以捉摸的
秘鲁果冻，
for flavor,
为了风味，
and it's only an extra...
而且这只是一个额外的...
$100 million charge?
Hm?
收费1亿美元？
嗯？
- That seems
slightly exorbitant,
- 看来
稍微有点过高,
but really, what's a measly
$100 million
但说实话，这算什么微不足道的事
1亿美元
to someone like me?
对于像我这样的人？
[both laugh]
[两人都笑了]
- [scatting]
- [分散]
- Ah, just as well.
- 啊，也好。
I wasn't that hungry anyway.
反正我没那么饿。
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
[dejected musical cue]
[沮丧的音乐提示]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- Someone order
a rusty cab?
- 有人订购
生锈的出租车？
- I like string.
- 我喜欢绳子。
- Congratulations.
- 恭喜。
♪ ♪
[groans]
[呻吟]
- Hm?
- 嗯？
♪ ♪
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
Ow.
噢。
- Ah, there's nothing
quite like
- 啊，什么都没有
很喜欢
a brand-new shirt.
一件全新的衬衫。
Whoops.
Forgot the tag.
哎呀。
忘记标签了。
- I got it!
- 我得到了它！
[gibbers excitedly]
[兴奋地胡言乱语]
- [growls]
- [咆哮]
♪ ♪
- Ah!
Oof!
- 啊！
钱币！
♪ ♪
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
- Oops.
Sorry, Sandy.
- 哎呀。
对不起，桑迪。
♪ ♪
- [gurgling]
- [咯咯声]
♪ ♪
- Ah, nothing beats cashmere.
- 啊，没有什么比羊绒更好的了。
Oh, a bit warm
for a sweater today, though.
哦，有点温暖
不过今天要买一件毛衣。
- I can help!
- 我可以帮忙！
- No, no, no, no!
No, no, no--[gibbers]
- 不，不，不，不！
不，不，不——[胡言乱语]
Oh, come on!
哦，来吧！
♪ ♪
[monkeys hooting]
[猴子叫声]
- Oh.
- 哦。
- [laughs]
- [笑]
Ah...
啊...
- Oh.
- 哦。
[dejected grunt]
[沮丧的咕哝]
- [scatting]
- [分散]
[monkeys growl]
[猴子咆哮]
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
[monkeys hooting]
[猴子叫声]
[fanfare]
[大张旗鼓]
- [scatting fanfare]
- [大肆宣扬]
Let's see
that twine-twirling twit
让我们看看
那个扭动麻线的小家伙
try to unravel this!
尝试解开这个谜题！
Huh.
Huh?
呵呵。
啊？
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
Really?
Ouch!
真的吗？
哎哟!
♪ ♪
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
♪ ♪
- [yells]
- [大喊]
Ah!
啊!
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Patrick, hi.
帕特里克，嗨。
- You have a thing
on your thing.
- 你有一件事
关于你的事。
♪ ♪
- [SpongeBob laughing]
- [海绵宝宝大笑]
♪ ♪